Jacob M. Kerr

kerr.jm213@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a technical problem solver who is dedicated to the contribution of success, with a focus on professional communication, innovative solutions, and emerging technologies.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Assistant Project Manager - UI/UX Developer 12/2015 - 8/2018 Cooler Concepts. Inc.

- Managed existing Word Press based website while creating new style to adhere to updated brand standards.
- Developed new brand standards.
- Developed new marketing materials (catalog, email campaigns, social media).
- Managed customer expectations, while working with consultants, dealers, regional representatives, and fellow members of the Cooler Concepts' Project Management Team to find the most comprehensive solution for the customer's available cooler space.
- Developed and provided customers, consultants, and dealers with scale AutoCad drawings documenting the footprint and execution of proposed solutions.
- Priced and processed quotes through AutoQuotes, emailed quotes to dealers and representatives, and followed up with customers to ensure the best possible customer experience.
- Managed new and existing projects daily, as well as resourcing opportunities for new projects.

Industrial Labor - Project Manager / Team Leader / Quality Assurance / CNC Machine Operator

2001 - 2015

Overview

Prior to my education I worked in a variety of labor positions including:

- Logistics
- Manufacturing
- Construction
- Remodeling

My first experience with Project Management (2002) was at a contract position where I led a team of workers in the design and construction of a warehouse storage system, specifically long-term gravity fed stock replenishment storage for an automotive parts manufacturer.

SKILLS

Project Management

Team Building

Motivation & Leadership

Account Development

Campaign Development

Inbound Marketing

B2B Communications

HTML5

CSS3

Mobile-First (Bootstrap / Flexbox)

Javascript (Angular / React / Node / ES6)

Command Line Editing (browser-sync)

Action Script 3

WordPress

MySQL

Adobe Creative Programs

Web Design & Development

Intuitive design

Image optimization

Identity and branding

Interactive multimedia

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

Document Object Model (DOM)

Web Accessibility (Section 508 / WCAG)

Server side scripting (PHP / ASP)

AutoCAD 2015

AutoQuotes

Microsoft Office

EDUCATION

DeVry University

College of Media Arts & Technology

AA in Web Graphic Design (June 2015)

BS in Multimedia Design & Development (Oct 2009-present)